Other transparencies
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Other transparencies
2.1.5.2
Marist College
  Box 1593
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1
  Box 1594
- Other transparencies, 2.1.5.2
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Mountain with body of water before it], 1950; 1 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man kneeling on top of boat with camera; glacier ahead of them], 1950; 2 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Glacier], 1950; 3 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Close-up of man wearing sunglasses], 1950; 4 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Group of people unloading supplies from airplane], 1950; 5 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [View of vast, snowy land with a small tent set-up at right], 1950; 6 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [People carrying supplies to tent], 1950; 7 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Glacier], 1950; 8 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man holding an instrument, standing in front of tent], 1950; 9 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man holding ski poles on rocky hill side], 1950; 10 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man skiing in his underwear], 1950; 11 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Lowell Thomas on skiis], 1950; 12 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man holding camera in front of snowy land], 1950; 13 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man with blankets], 1950; 14 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Four men standing on rocks; Lowell Thomas second from right], 1950; 15 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Glacier], 1950; 16 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man on boat, snowy mountains in distance], 1950; 17 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [River running by mountains], 1950; 18 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Close-up of man wearing sunglasses], 1950; 19 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Profile of man looking out across water], 1950; 20 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Men unloading supplies from airplane], 1950; 21 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Men unloading supplies from airplane, Lowell Thomas in front], 1950; 22 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Three men crouched], 1950; 23 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man climbing a weathervane], 1950; 24 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Mountains with body of water before them], 1950; 25 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [People gathered around an airplane], 1950; 26 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [People loading (or unloading) supplies onto plane], 1950; 27 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Iceberg], 1950; 28 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Iceberg], 1950; 29 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man with camera set up on rocks], 1950; 30 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Close-up of man holding camera], 1950; 31 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Two men in uniform standing in front of airplane], 1950; 32 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man at edge of boat, mountatins in distance], 1950; 33 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [River running by mountains], 1950; 34 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Glacier], 1950; 35 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Two men at left. Airplane on runway], 1950; 36 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Glacier], 1950; 37 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Vast snowy land with tents set up], 1950; 38 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man standing among skiis stuck in snow], 1950; 39 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man looking at instrument], 1950; 40 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man by tent, another man shoveling snow], 1950; 41 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Men wearing skiis, pulling a sled], 1950; 42 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man with box attached to his back], 1950; 43 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Men walking through snow with boxes attached to their backs], 1950; 44 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man standing in snow], 1950; 45 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man standing in snow], 1950; 46 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Men setting up tent?], 1950; 47 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man wearing sunglasses on skiis], 1950; 48 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Men setting up tent?], 1950; 49 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Men setting up tent?], 1950; 50 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Two men talking], 1950; 51 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Two men wearing sunglasses, posing for picture], 1950; 52 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Two men working on equipment], 1950; 53 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man closely examining an object], 1950; 54 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man looking though a microscope], 1950; 55 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man wearing sunglasses looking at an object], 1950; 56 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [People walking through snow, mountains ahead of them], 1950; 57 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Shack sitting on top of rocks], 1950; 58 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Shack sitting on top of rocks], 1950; 59 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man standing on rocks], 1950; 60 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [American flag stuck between rocks], 1950; 61 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Skiis laid out near rocks], 1950; 62 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [American flag stuck in rocks at right], 1950; 63 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [American flag stuck in rocks at left], 1950; 64 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man with pipe in his mouth, another man with a horn], 1950; 65 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man crouched with pipe in his mouth, looking at object], 1950; 66 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man with pipe in mouth, examining some type of equipment], 1950; 67 (Box 1594)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man sitting down, smiling], 1950; 68 (Box 1594)
  Box 1595
- Other transparencies, 2.1.5.2
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man holding a pan], 1950; 1 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Two men. One writing in notebook. (doctor?)], 1950; 2 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man on skiis with backpack], 1950; 3 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man on skiis with box on back], 1950; 4 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man working on skiis], 1950; 5 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Lowell Thomas eating], 1950; 6 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man sitting on rocks], 1950; 7 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man eating sandwich], 1950; 8 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man eating], 1950; 9 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man eating], 1950; 10 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Two men sitting on rocks, eating], 1950; 11 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man with backpack], 1950; 12 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Three men standing, smoking], 1950; 13 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Two men, one holding a device], 1950; 14 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Three man outside of shack], 1950; 15 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Two men standing outside of shack], 1950; 16 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Four men outside of shack], 1950; 17 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Snowcapped mountains in distance], 1950; 18 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man working at desk], 1950; 19 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Two men, one on phone], 1950; 20 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man with sunglasses, holding a horn], 1950; 21 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man on skiis], 1950; 22 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Skiis stuck in snow, backpack], 1950; 23 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Snowy hill], 1950; 24 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Snowy hill, man in the distance], 1950; 25 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Snowy hill, two people in distance], 1950; 26 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man standing on rock], 1950; 27 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man standing on rock], 1950; 28 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Snowy land, person at right], 1950; 29 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Three men on skiis], 1950; 30 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Three men on skiis], 1950; 31 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man in underwear on skiis], 1950; 32 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man in underwear on skiis], 1950; 33 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Two men on skiis], 1950; 34 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Three men, one climbing down a ladder into a trench], 1950; 35 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man on skiis], 1950; 36 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man on skiis], 1950; 37 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Snowy hill, two people on skiis], 1950; 38 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man in underwear lying on rocks], 1950; 39 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [A trench], 1950; 40 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Looking up from the bottom of a trench], 1950; 41 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Three men, one climbing down a ladder into a trench], 1950; 42 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man on ladder], 1950; 43 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Inside trench], 1950; 44 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Snowy mountains], 1950; 45 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [American flag stuck in rocks], 1950; 46 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [American flag stuck in rocks], 1950; 47 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [American flag stuck in rocks], 1950; 48 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Snowy mountains], 1950; 49 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Sun peeking out from behind snowy mountains], 1950; 50 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [People on boat in icy water], 1950; 51 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Tugboat on icy water], 1950; 52 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Icy water], 1950; 53 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Icy water], 1950; 54 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man on ice with camera], 1950; 55 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Airplane side propellers], 1950; 56 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Airplane on runway], 1950; 57 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Icy water], 1950; 58 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Icy water], 1950; 59 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Icy water], 1950; 60 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Icy water], 1950; 61 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Icy water], 1950; 62 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Icy water and snowy mountain], 1950; 63 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Mountain], 1950; 64 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Water running by mountains], 1950; 65 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Water running by mountains], 1950; 66 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Captain], 1950; 67 (Box 1595)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Men sitting in boat], 1950; 68 (Box 1595)
  Box 1596
- Other transparencies, 2.1.5.2
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Icy water running by mountains], 1950; 1 (Box 1596)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man sitting on rocks], 1950; 2 (Box 1596)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [American flag stuck in rocks. Man standing on rocks], 1950; 3 (Box 1596)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man eating fish from a can], 1950; 4 (Box 1596)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Rocky side], 1950; 5 (Box 1596)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Two men standing on rocks], 1950; 6 (Box 1596)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Tugboat on water], 1950; 7 (Box 1596)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Ladder leading down trench], 1950; 8 (Box 1596)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Three men standing on rocks, Lowell Thomas standing in the middle], 1950; 9 (Box 1596)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Two men by American flag. One man holding a horn], 1950; 10 (Box 1596)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Lowell Thomas and two other men sitting, eating from cans], 1950; 11 (Box 1596)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Man standing on rocks, looking out], 1950; 12 (Box 1596)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Lowell Thomas sitting outside of tent, man standing], 1950; 13 (Box 1596)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Lowell Thomas talking with another man], 1950; 14 (Box 1596)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Lowell Thomas on rocks with another man smoking a pipe], 1950; 15 (Box 1596)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Lowell Thomas standing with another man], 1950; 16 (Box 1596)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Group of men with skiis and sled, Lowell Thomas at right], 1950; 17 (Box 1596)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Lowell Thomas talking with another man], 1950; 18 (Box 1596)
  - Alaska (Lowell Thomas) [Lowell Thomas and another man sitting in boat on water], 1950; 19 (Box 1596)